<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>
<configuration>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.master.port</name>
    <value>60000</value>
    <description>The port the HBase Master should bind to.</description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>zookeeper.znode.parent</name>
    <value>/hbase96</value>
    <description>Root ZNode for HBase in ZooKeeper. All of HBase's ZooKeeper
      files that are configured with a relative path will go under this node.
      By default, all of HBase's ZooKeeper file path are configured with a
      relative path, so they will all go under this directory unless changed.
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.client.write.buffer</name>
    <value>5242880</value>
    <description>Default size of the HTable clien write buffer in bytes.
    A bigger buffer takes more memory -- on both the client and server
    side since server instantiates the passed write buffer to process
    it -- but a larger buffer size reduces the number of RPCs made.
    For an estimate of server-side memory-used, evaluate
    hbase.client.write.buffer * hbase.regionserver.handler.count
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.client.pause</name>
    <value>500</value>
    <description>General client pause value.  Used mostly as value to wait
    before running a retry of a failed get, region lookup, etc.</description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.client.retries.number</name>
    <value>20</value>
    <description>Maximum retries.  Used as maximum for all retryable
    operations such as fetching of the root region from root region
    server, getting a cell's value, starting a row update, etc.
    Default: 10.
    </description>
  </property> 
  <property>
    <name>hbase.bulkload.retries.number</name>
    <value>10</value>
    <description>Maximum retries.  This is maximum number of iterations
    to atomic bulk loads are attempted in the face of splitting operations
    0 means never give up.  Default: 0.
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.client.scanner.caching</name>
    <value>100</value>
    <description>Number of rows that will be fetched when calling next
    on a scanner if it is not served from (local, client) memory. Higher
    caching values will enable faster scanners but will eat up more memory
    and some calls of next may take longer and longer times when the cache is empty.
    Do not set this value such that the time between invocations is greater
    than the scanner timeout; i.e. hbase.regionserver.lease.period
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.client.keyvalue.maxsize</name>
    <value>10485760</value>
    <description>Specifies the combined maximum allowed size of a KeyValue
    instance. This is to set an upper boundary for a single entry saved in a
    storage file. Since they cannot be split it helps avoiding that a region
    cannot be split any further because the data is too large. It seems wise
    to set this to a fraction of the maximum region size. Setting it to zero
    or less disables the check.
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>zookeeper.session.timeout</name>
    <value>180000</value>
    <description>ZooKeeper session timeout.
      HBase passes this to the zk quorum as suggested maximum time for a
      session (This setting becomes zookeeper's 'maxSessionTimeout').  See
      http://hadoop.apache.org/zookeeper/docs/current/zookeeperProgrammers.html#ch_zkSessions
      "The client sends a requested timeout, the server responds with the
      timeout that it can give the client. " In milliseconds.
    </description>
  </property>
   <property>
    <name>hbase.zookeeper.quorum</name>
    <value>hadoop01,hadoop02,hadoop03,hadoop05</value>
    <description>Comma separated list of servers in the ZooKeeper Quorum.
    For example, "host1.mydomain.com,host2.mydomain.com,host3.mydomain.com".
    By default this is set to localhost for local and pseudo-distributed modes
    of operation. For a fully-distributed setup, this should be set to a full
    list of ZooKeeper quorum servers. If HBASE_MANAGES_ZK is set in hbase-env.sh
    this is the list of servers which we will start/stop ZooKeeper on.
    </description>
  </property>
  <property>
    <name>hbase.zookeeper.property.clientPort</name>
    <value>2181</value>
    <description>Property from ZooKeeper's config zoo.cfg.
    The port at which the clients will connect.
    </description>
  </property>
    
</configuration>
